# ADEGBAYE ADEDOLAPO ADETOMI

+234 07037837184 | adedolapoadegbaye@gmail.com | Lekki Ajah, Lagos State, Nigeria

# **PROFILE SUMMARY**

**Resourceful Administrative Officer and Educator** with 8 years of experience in office management, administrative coordination, customer relationship management, and business strategy. Possess comprehensive experience coordinating office operations and performing detailed administrative support functions. Demonstrated commitment to providing incredible service, balancing company goals while helping all customers find satisfactory solutions. An unwavering commitment to customer service, with the ability to build productive relationships, resolve complex issues and win customer loyalty. Excellent track record of building strategic relationships with customers to understand solutions that meet their needs.

#### **CORE COMPETENCIES**

- Administrative Management
- Customer Service
- Customer Relationship Management (CRM)
- Compliance Monitoring
- Database Management
- Organizational Development
- Human Resources

- Problem Solving
- Process Improvement
- Training & Development
- Team Leadership

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Administrative Officer - Grace Meridian School.

Jan. 2022 - Sept. 2022

- Monitored the school's overall performance, continually improved the syllabus, and took appropriate steps to improve its
  effectiveness.
- Kept track of students' successes and failures and prepared appropriate interventions to maintain the school's record of producing excellent students.
- Ensured the school complied with relevant laws and regulations to maintain good standards and reputation.
- Established and maintained good relationships with parents, students, and staff at the school to build a friendly and welcoming atmosphere.

#### Educator - Paves International School.

Sept. 2020 - Sept. 2021

- Supervised classes to ensure all students were learning in a safe and productive environment, thereby promoting the assimilation rate.
- Developed lesson notes and issued educational content, including notes, tests, and assignments, to facilitate learning.
- Delivered personalized instructions to each student by encouraging interactive learning.
- Graded and recorded students' homework, tests and exams to provide mark records and reports.

# **Educator** – PASMAC Montessori School.

Jun. 2017 - Feb. 2020

- Executed educational in-class and outdoor activities and events to introduce entertainment in education for faster retention.
- Planned lessons and activities that facilitated students' acquisition of basic and advanced academic and real-life application skills.
- Instructed students in a way that developed their confidence in their abilities to enable proactive learning.
- Collaborated with other teachers, parents and stakeholders and participated in regular meetings for progressive agendas.

# Office Assistant (Education Dept.) - IRU/VI LCDA Victoria Island, Lagos (NYSC).

May. 2016 - Apr. 2017

- Organized a filing system for important and confidential company documents to maintain proper office standards.
- Maintained and updated the office's financial records to provide adequate record-keeping.
- Prepared regular reports on expenses and office budgets for adequate documentation.
- Provided answers and solutions to employee and client queries, complaints and enquiries.
- Greeted visitors and pointed them in the right direction, answered inquiries, and created a welcoming environment.

# **Customer Service Representative** – Pitch Travels and Tours Ltd.

Jul. 2016 - Aug. 2016

- Recommended potential services to management by collecting customer information and analyzing customer needs to improve the quality of service.
- Engaged customers online and on call about new products and assisted them with their orders and enquiries.

- Resolved problems by the customer's complaint, determining the cause of the problem, selecting and explaining the best solution to solve the problem, expediting correction or adjustment and following up to ensure resolution.
- Prepared reports regularly by collecting and analyzing customer information to improve customer satisfaction.
- Utilized interactive communication skills to forge sustainable relationships and trust with customers.

# **Educator** – PASMAC Montessori School.

2014 - 2016

- Collaborated with other teachers to organize vocabulary development competitions, improving students' spoken and written English.
- Maintained quality classroom and behaviour management while ensuring all students improved morally and academically.
- Developed and implemented an effective teaching style to maintain attention and discipline to foster student retention.

# **EDUCATION**

•	Bachelor of Arts in English – Obafemi Awolowo University, Osun State, Nigeria.	2014
CERTIFICATES AND PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATIONS		
•	Member - Charity CDS Group, IRU/VI LCDA	2016
•	Certified Customer Service Associate (CCSA)	2013
•	Certified Senior Customer Service Professional (CSCSP)	2013